Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel-to-reel tapes, 1983-1993, II.; Reel 1-22
  - WNED Radio Program featuring North American New Music Festival Concert 23: Part 2, 1984-04-11, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 2 of 2 for program. Noted as being part of the radio series, Music in Buffalo, 85-15, April 8, 1985. (Box 9, Reel Reel 12)
    Intermission filler with commentary and excerpts played from music by Messiaen, Mel Powell, Holst, Stravinsky, and Arthur Sullivan
    Note: Note: Files for this reel named based on the assumption that reels change where the station identification is indicated. Contents in this segment: Olivier Messiaen: Sept Haikai. Gagaku (Musical Heritage Society 3031); Mel Powell: Haiku settings: Icy the moonshine (Nonesuch 78006); Gustav Holst: Japanese suite. Dance under the cherry tree (Musical Heritage Society 1919); Igor Stravinsky: Three Japanese lyrics (Chandos 1048); Arthur Sullivan: Mikado. Excerpt (London 12103)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_402_02
    Introduction for performance of Kenneth Sullivan's Wonderful time, including interview with Yvar Mikhashoff
    Note: Note: Files for this reel named based on the assumption that reels change where the station identification is indicated. Contents need to be confirmed.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_402_03
    Wonderful time (1984)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_03sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_402_04
    Introduction for performance of Charles Casavant's Gently turns, including interview with Yvar Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_04pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_04sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_402_05
    Casavant, Charles Ewing, 1945-
    Gently turns (1983)
    Duration: 6:52
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_05pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_05sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_402_06
    Introduction for performance of Netty Simon's Cityscape no. 2, including interview with Yvar Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_06pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_06sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_402_07
    Simons, Netty
    Cityscape no. 2 (1984)
    Duration: 13:19
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_07pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_07sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_402_08
    Closing comments for program and closing theme music
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_402am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_402_08pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_402_08sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio Program featuring North American New Music Festival Concert 30: Part 1, 1985-04-13, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 1 of 2 for program. Noted as being part of the radio series, Music in Buffalo, 86-13, March 31, 1986. (Box 9, Reel Reel 13)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_01
    Theme music and introduction for performance of William Ortiz's Llego la banda, including interview with Ortiz
    Performers: Leila Lustig, announcer and William Ortiz, composer
    Note: Noted as being part of the radio series, Music in Buffalo, 86-13, March 31, 1986
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_02
    Ortiz, William
    Llego la banda (1984)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_03
    Introduction for performance of Philip Glass's, including interview with Yvar Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_03sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_04
    Glass, Philip
    Einstein on the beach. Knee play no. 2
    Duration: 11:36
    Note: On original printed program as Glass's Strung out
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_04pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_04sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_05
    Introduction for performance of Lejaren Hiller's The fox trots again, including interview with Hiller
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_05pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_05sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_06
    Fox trots again (1984)
    Duration: 4:28
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_06pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_06sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_07
    Introduction for performance of Leonard Bernstein's Touches, including interview with Yvar Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_07pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_07sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_08
    Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990
    Touches (1980)
    Duration: 8:52
    Note: Note that a stage light blows out during the performance
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_08pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_08sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_09
    Introduction for performance of Wayang II by Anthony, including interview with Yvar Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_09pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_09sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_10
    Davis, Anthony, 1951
    Wayang II (1981)
    Duration: 6:07
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_10pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_10sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_403_11
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_403am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_403_11pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_403_11sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio Program featuring North American New Music Festival Concert 30: Part 2, 1985-04-13, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 2 of 2 for program. (Box 9, Reel Reel 14)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_404_01
    Introduction for performance of Grand pianola music by John Adams, including interview with Yvar Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_404am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_404_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_404_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_404_02
    Adams, John, 1947-
    Grand pianola music (1982)
    Duration: 33:38
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_404am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_404_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_404_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_404_03
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_404am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_404_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_404_03sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_405_01
    Theme music and introduction for performance of Steve Reich's Music for mallet instruments
    Note: Noted as being part of the radio series, Music in Buffalo, 86-14, April 7, 1986
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_405am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_405_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_405_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_405_02
    Reich, Steve, 1936-
    Music for mallet instruments, voices, and organ(1973)
    Venue: Holy Trinity Lutheran Church (Buffalo, N.Y.)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_405am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_405_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_405_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_405_03
    Introduction for performance of Colin Bright's Red earth, including interview with Bright
    Performers: Leila Lustig, announcer and Colin Bright, composer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_405am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_405_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_405_03sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_405_04
    Bright, Colin
    Red earth (1985)
    Duration: 8:32
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_405am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_405_04pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_405_04sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_405_05
    Introduction for performance of Chester Biscardi's Piano concerto, including interview with Biscardi
    Performers: Leila Lustig, announcer and Chester Biscardi, composer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_405am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_405_05pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_405_05sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_405_06
    Biscardi, Chester
    Concerto, piano (1984)
    Duration: 18:46
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_405am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_405_06pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_405_06sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_405_07
    Introduction for performance Lou Harrison's Organ concerto
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_405am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_405_07pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_405_07sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio Program featuring North American New Music Festival Concert 37 and 39: Part 1, 1985-04-16 and 1985-04-17, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 1 of 3 for program. Noted as being part of the radio series, Music in Buffalo, 86-14, April 7, 1986. (Box 9, Reel Reel 15)
  - WNED Radio Program featuring North American New Music Festival Concert 37 and 39: Part 2, 1985-04-16 and 1985-04-17, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 2 of 3 for program. (Box 9, Reel Reel 16)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_406_01
    Continuation of introduction for performance Lou Harrison's Organ concerto
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_406am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_406_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_406_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_406_02
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003
    Concerto, organ (1973)
    Duration: 26:36
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_406am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_406_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_406_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_406_03
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_406am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_406_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_406_03sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio Program featuring North American New Music Festival Concert 37 and 39: Part 3, 1985-04-16 and 1985-04-17, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 3 of 3 for program. (Box 9, Reel Reel 17)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_01
    Introduction for performance of Bruce Penner's Buffalo roam, including interview with Penner
    Performers: Leila Lustig, announcer and Bruce Penner, composer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_02
    Penner, Bruce
    Buffalo roam (1985)
    Duration: 15:20
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_03
    Introduction for performance of William Russell's March suite
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_03sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_04
    Russell, Bill, 1905-1992
    March suite (1933-36)
    Duration: 4:07
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_04pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_04sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_05
    Introduction for performance of William Russell's Three Cuban dances
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_05pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_05sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_06
    Three Cuban dances (1934)
    Duration: 3:20
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_06pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_06sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_07
    Introduction for performance of William Russell's Prelude, choral and fugue
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_07pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_07sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_08
    Prelude, chorale / Fugue (1984, 1933)
    Duration: 6:53
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_08pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_08sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_09
    Introduction for performance of John Bergamo's Interactions, including interview with Bergamo
    Performers: Leila Lustig, announcer and John Bergamo, composer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_09pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_09sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_10
    Bergamo, John
    Interactions (1961)
    Duration: 8:21
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_10pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_10sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_11
    Introduction for performance of John Bergamo's Shradanjali, including interview with Bergamo
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_11pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_11sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_12
    Shradhanjali (1980)
    Duration: 10:02
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_12pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_12sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_407_13
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_407am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_407_13pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_407_13sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio recording of North American New Music Festival Concert 60, 1986-04-16, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Note that there was no radio script found with this item so it is unclear if it only contains the concert performances or additional radio commentary. (Box 9, Reel Reel 18)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_408_01
    Tower, Joan, 1938-
    Petroushskates
    Note: Note that there was no radio script found with this item so it is unclear if it only contains the concert performances or additional radio commentary. Confirm contents
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_408am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_408_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_408_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_408_02
    Vermont counterpoint
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_408am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_408_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_408_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_408_03
    Felder, David, 1953-
    Passageways II
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_408am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_408_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_408_03sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_408_04
    Modern love waltz
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_408am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_408_04pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_408_04sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_408_05
    Stock, David, 1939-2015
    Sulla spiaggia
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_408am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_408_05pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_408_05sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_408_06
    Morris, Robert, 1943-
    Saraswati's children
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_408am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_408_06pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_408_06sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio recording of last work on North American New Music Festival Concert 60 and separate Ursula Openns concert, 1986-04-16 and 1986-04-22, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Contains only the first three works of the Oppens program. (Box 9, Reel Reel 19)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_409_01
    Block, Steven D., 1952-
    Rockin' pneumonia
    Note: Concert recording; preceded by spoken introduction
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_409am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_409_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_409_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_409_02
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750
    Partitas, harpsichord, BWV 829, G major
    Performers: Ursula Oppens, piano
    Note: Concert recording. The date matches a non-NANMF concert by Ursula Oppens. The contents have been supplied from that program. Confirm contents
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_409am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_409_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_409_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_409_03
    Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827
    Sonatas, piano, no. 32, op. 111, C minor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_409am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_409_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_409_03sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio recording of North American New Music Festival Concert 111: Part 1, 1988-03-19, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 1 of 2 of concert. Concert recording. A program marked by a sound engineer was inserted. (Box 9, Reel Reel 20)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_410_01
    Fifth simfony (1939)
    Duration: 15:47
    Note: Concert recording. A program marked by a sound engineer was inserted. Contents are supplied from that program.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_410am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_410_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_410_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_410_02
    Ariadne (1987)
    Duration: 6:46
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_410am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_410_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_410_02sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_410_03
    Summerfield set (1988)
    Duration: 12:12
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_410am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_410_03pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_410_03sc.mp3
  - WNED Radio recording of North American New Music Festival Concert 111: Part 2, 1988-03-19, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips Tape 2 of 2 of concert. Concert recording. A program marked by a sound engineer was inserted. (Box 9, Reel Reel 21)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_411_01
    Labyrinth no. 3 (1940-41)
    Duration: 18:34
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_411am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_411_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_411_01sc.mp3
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_411_02
    Duration: 25:57
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_411am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_411_02pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_411_02sc.mp3
  - North American New Music Festival Concert 29, 1984-04-14, 1 10-inch reel of 1/4 audio tape; 2-channel stereo., 7.5 ips This tape was not part of the WNED holdings. It is assumed to be a recording of the NANMF performance but there is no marking other than composer and title. The inserted program was supplied based on that assumption. (Box 9, Reel Reel 22)
    File/Work number: ubmu0013_1_412_01
    Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1928-2007
    Mantra (1970)
    Duration: 1:07:47
    Note: This tape was not part of the WNED holdings. It is assumed to be a recording of the NANMF performance but there is no marking other than composer and title. The inserted program was supplied based on that assumption.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_412am.wav; Production master file: ubmu0013_1_412_01pm.mp3; Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_412_01sc.mp3
- Hard drives and accompanying documentation, 2017-2018, III.; 2 hard drives and 1 binder
  Two hard drives containing reformatted digital audio and metadata files for the cassettes and reels respectively and a notebook binder containing photocopies of the Festival programs, list of concert dates, list of works performed, and scripts for the WNED radio programs.
  - Hard drive containing digital audio and metadata files for Cassettes 1-390, 2017, 1 TB hard drive (Box 10, Item 1)
  - Hard drive containing digital audio and metadata files for Reels 1-22, 2018, 1 TB hard drive (Box 10, Item 3)
  - Binder of accompanying documentation, 2017-2018, 1 binder (Box 10, Item 3)
    Three-ring binder contains photocopies of the Festival programs, a list of concert dates, a list of works performed, and scripts for the WNED radio programs.
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Contributors
Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993; Williams, Jan, 1939-
Subjects
Music--20th century; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo; North American New Music Festival (Buffalo, N.Y.)
Genres
sound recordings
Associated Material
Separated Material
The following 217 musical works were performed during the North American New Music Festival but not recorded. In the original inventory they were assigned work numbers and were stated within the list where they chronologically occurred in the programming. The works are listed by the original numbering. They are included here to show the entire performed content of the festival. However, as a list of works never recorded, it does not truly represent anything physically separated from the collection.
NAF 005A. McLean, Priscilla: Inner universe (1982), on North American New Music Festival Concert 002, April 6, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 005B. McLean, Priscilla: Invisible chariots (1975-77), on North American New Music Festival Concert 002, April 6, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 006A. McLean, Barton: Dimensions VIII (1982), on North American New Music Festival Concert 002, April 6, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 006B. McLean, Barton: Last ten minutes (1982), on North American New Music Festival Concert 002, April 6, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 044A. Austin, Larry: Tableaux vivants (1981), on North American New Music Festival Concert 011, April 12, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 055a. Kotík, Petr: Variations (1977-1982), on North American New Music Festival Concert 014, April 15, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 055b. Kotík, Petr: Solos and incidental harmonies (1983), on North American New Music Festival Concert 014, April 15, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 061A. Uitti, Frances-Marie: Museum walk improvisations, on North American New Music Festival Concert 016, April 10, 1984, 6:00 p.m.
NAF 061B. Multiple composers: Seventy works in seventy years in celebration... (1914-1984), on North American New Music Festival Concert 017, April 8, 1984, 5:00 p.m.
NAF 067A. Zappa, Frank: Pedro's dowry, on North American New Music Festival Concert 020, April 9, 1984, 8:00 p.m.